<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	<htmlContent tag="CHU_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While many of these strange monsters are new to Lilith's Realm, these rodents have become exceptionally popular, especially in Dominion. Members of the Pikachu & Raichu family can be swiftly identified with their warm fur colors, puffy cheeks, pointy ears, and distinct lightning bolt shaped tails.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="CHU_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldORANGE(Raichu)]
	</p>
	<p>
		This mouse-like creature is capable of holding large amounts of electrical power in its body, channeled through its cheeks. Raichu can be identified via its curly ears, orange fur, and long, thin tails with a lightning-bolt shape at the end. The bolts of a female Raichu's tail have a flattened tip at the end not present in males.
	</p>
	<p>
		It originally harvested electric energy from passing storms and urban power-lines. In its original world, it could hold enough voltage to bring down elephants and other creatures several times its size. However, exposure to Lilith's Domain have made Raichu receptive to arcane energies.
	</p>
	<p>
		Storing too much arcane power will send Raichu into an aggressive rut, with arcane storms making them especially dangerous and horny. In such a state, it will ground itself with its long tail to disperse any electric or arcane power in an attempt to calm itself down. If this doesn't work, it will attempt to dominate any passers-by in another attempt to "ground" itself.
	</p>
	<p>
		The harpies of Dominion are split in regards to the treatment & welcome of Raichu. On one hand, the more domineering side of the Harpy Nests don't take kindly to the errant arcane jolts these critters attract, and demand they be put in their place in Submission, far away from their kind. In contrast, the more submissive harpy citizens have taken a shine to the domineering nature of "overcharged" Raichu, with some even keeping them as personal "pets" that can turn the tables on them at a moment's notice.
	</p>
	<p>
		Unlike normal rodents, or most other mammals for that matter, Raichu deliver their offspring by laying eggs. While their form at birth naturally shifts and evolves as a result of Lilith's arcane influence, their sexual disposition seems to be active even at a more supposedly juvenile age. (Though not quite as instantaneous as some other "monsters".)
	</p>
	<p>
		Using an Everstone on a Raichu will cause them to regress into Pikachu.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldBROWN(Alolan Raichu)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Unlike their more wild counterparts, these particular breed of Raichu are more civil and approachable in their disposition. Their features are much more rounded and their tails have grown to the point where they can be seen "surfing" atop them, telepathically floating.
	</p>
	<p>
		Its powers are unique compared to other Raichu, bearing telekinetic abilities and emitting unique star-shaped volts from its cheeks. These abilities have allowed these Raichu to harness arcane energy far more effectively than it's other form.
	</p>
	<p>
		These psychic mice are far more sociable than other Raichu, often taking up jobs at different urban locales. They seem to have a natural addiction to delicious, fluffy pancakes, to the point where even their cheeks start to emit a sweet smell at the mere thought of them.
	</p>
	<p>
		While the presence of Raichu are heavily contested by the harpies of Dominion, the "pancake-variety" are notably more favored by the citizens of the nest, with their more mild dispositions being just as willing to submit as they are to dominate.
	</p>
	<p>
		Like other Raichu, Alolan Raichu lay eggs to deliver their young. Their pack nature combined with their friendliness toward civilized areas often lead to the community helping to raise their young.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using an Everstone on a "Pancake" Raichu will also cause them to regress into Pikachu. Apparently you can tell by the look in a Pikachu's eyes which form of Raichu they'll evolve into.
	</p>
	<br/>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldYELLOW(Pikachu)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The juvenile form of Raichu. While their round face, bolt-shaped tail, and puffy red cheeks are incredibly appealing, these mouse-like creatures aren't quite as populous as their more matured counterparts, due to requiring certain stones to change to and from said forms.
	</p>
	<p>
		Much like their parent race, Pikachu's electrical affinity has been translated into that of the arcane in this realm. With their tails acting as a sort of weather radar, Pikachu are often the first to know of an approaching arcane storm.
	</p>
	<p>
		In their original world, Pikachu and Raichu gathered en masse in secluded forest grottos, forming thriving communities, often greeting or reenergizing each other through electric shocks. Attempts to replicate this behavior in Lilith's Domain have often resulted in massive orgies.
	</p>
	<p>
		Pikachu tend to have less control over their cheeks (either of them) than Raichu do, and are often kept far away from the Harpy Nests. (with very few exceptions, you can only stay away from cute for so long)
	</p>
	<p>
		Pikachu also lay eggs once they've finished gestating. Both Raichu & Pikachu eggs normally hatch into a creature called Pichu. While this form and Pikachu are quickly skipped over when Raichu eggs hatch (due to Lilith's influence), Pikachu that lay their offspring tend to finish growing while they're still Pikachu.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using a Thunder Stone on a Pikachu will evolve it into one of two forms of Raichu.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
</bookText>
