<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!-- For a version with comments, see "rental_mommy.xml". -->
<clothing>
	<coreAttributes>
		<value>3000</value>
		<determiner><![CDATA[an]]></determiner>
		<name><![CDATA[Illusionary Seal - Belly Maw]]></name>
		<namePlural pluralByDefault="false"><![CDATA[Illusionary Seals - Belly Maw]]></namePlural>
		<description><![CDATA[A piece of enchanted paper that, when applied, creates a localised glamour that makes one's stomach look like the mouth of a toothy beast. Anyone brave enough to stick their hand in will find the truth quite quickly however, as it does not provide tactile sensation.]]></description>
		<physicalResistance>1</physicalResistance>
		<femininity>ANDROGYNOUS</femininity>
		<slot>STOMACH</slot>
		<rarity>RARE</rarity>
		<clothingSet/>
		<imageName>BellyMawSeal.svg</imageName>
		<imageEquippedName>BellyMaw.svg</imageEquippedName>
		<enchantmentLimit/>
		<effects>
              <effect itemEffectType="CLOTHING" limit="0" potency="MINOR_BOOST" primaryModifier="CLOTHING_SEALING" secondaryModifier="ARCANE_BOOST" timer="0"/>
		</effects>
		<blockedPartsList>
			<blockedParts>
				<displacementType>REMOVE_OR_EQUIP</displacementType>
				<clothingAccessRequired>
					<clothingAccess>WAIST</clothingAccess>
				</clothingAccessRequired>
				<blockedBodyParts/>
				<clothingAccessBlocked/>
				<concealedSlots/>
			</blockedParts>

		</blockedPartsList>
		<incompatibleSlots>PIERCING_STOMACH</incompatibleSlots>
		<primaryColours values="JUST_DARK_RED"/>
		<primaryColoursDye values="ALL"/>
		<itemTags>
			<tag>SOLD_BY_KATE</tag>
			<tag>TRANSPARENT</tag>
		</itemTags>
	</coreAttributes>

	<displacementText type="REMOVE_OR_EQUIP">
		<playerSelf><![CDATA[
			You reach inside your second mouth and feel around till you brush against the corner of the paper resting on your stomach. With a quick pinch and tug, the illusion dissipates in a puff of arcane smoke, leaving the deactivated seal in your hand.
		]]></playerSelf>
		<playerNPC><![CDATA[
			You reach inside [npc.name]'s second mouth and feel around till you brush against the corner of the paper resting on [npc.herHis] stomach. With a quick pinch and tug, the illusion dissipates in a puff of arcane smoke, leaving the deactivated seal in your hand.
		]]></playerNPC>
		<playerNPCRough><![CDATA[
			You thrust your hand inside [npc.name]'s second mouth so roughly it would have gagged were it real. You grope around at [npc.herHis] stomach till you brush against the corner of the paper resting in the centre, and yank it off. The illusion dissipates in a puff of arcane smoke, leaving the deactivated seal in your hand.
		]]></playerNPCRough>
		<NPCSelf><![CDATA[
			[npc.Name] reaches inside [npc.herHis] second mouth and feels around till [npc.she] brushes against the corner of the paper resting on [npc.herHis] stomach. With a quick pinch and tug, the illusion dissipates in a puff of arcane smoke, leaving the deactivated seal in [npc.herHis] hand.
		]]></NPCSelf>
		<NPCPlayer><![CDATA[
			[npc.Name] reaches inside your second mouth and feels around till [npc.she] brushes against the corner of the paper resting on your stomach. With a quick pinch and tug, the illusion dissipates in a puff of arcane smoke, leaving the deactivated seal in [npc.herHis] hand.
		]]></NPCPlayer>
		<NPCPlayerRough><![CDATA[
			[npc.Name] thrusts [npc.herHis] hand inside your second mouth so roughly it would have gagged were it real. [npc.She] gropes around at your stomach till [npc.she] brushes against the corner of the paper resting in the centre, and yanks it off. The illusion dissipates in a puff of arcane smoke, leaving the deactivated seal in [npc.herHis] hand.
		]]></NPCPlayerRough>
		<NPCOtherNPC><![CDATA[
			[npc1.Name] reaches inside [npc2.name]'s second mouth and feels around till [npc1.she] brushes against the corner of the paper resting on [npc2.herHis] stomach. With a quick pinch and tug, the illusion dissipates in a puff of arcane smoke, leaving the deactivated seal in [npc1.herHis] hand.
		]]></NPCOtherNPC>
		<NPCOtherNPCRough><![CDATA[
			[npc1.Name] thrusts [npc1.herHis] hand inside [npc2.name]'s second mouth so roughly it would have gagged were it real. [npc1.She] gropes around at [npc2.herHis] stomach till [npc1.she] brushes against the corner of the paper resting in the centre, and yanks it off. The illusion dissipates in a puff of arcane smoke, leaving the deactivated seal in [npc1.herHis] hand.
		]]></NPCOtherNPCRough>
	</displacementText>

	<replacementText type="REMOVE_OR_EQUIP">
		<playerSelf><![CDATA[
			You place the seal onto your belly, and marvel as it seems to sink into your skin. Your skin splits open painlessly the next second forming jagged teeth and a lolling tongue, however a testing reach for them has your hands waving through thin air, and brushing against your [pc.skinSkin+] half way into the illusionary maw.
		]]></playerSelf>
		<playerNPC><![CDATA[
			You place the seal onto [npc.name]'s belly, and marvel as it seems to sink into [npc.herHis] skin. [npc.HerHis] skin splits open painlessly the next second forming jagged teeth and a lolling tongue.
		]]></playerNPC>
		<playerNPCRough><![CDATA[
			You press the seal onto [npc.name]'s belly, and hold it down until it seems to sink into [npc.herHis] skin. [npc.HerHis] skin splits open painlessly the next second forming jagged teeth and a lolling tongue.
		]]></playerNPCRough>
		<NPCSelf><![CDATA[
			[npc.Name] places the seal onto [npc.herHis]'s belly, and marvels as it seems to sink into [npc.herHis] skin. [npc.HerHis] skin splits open painlessly the next second forming jagged teeth and a lolling tongue.
		]]></NPCSelf>
		<NPCPlayer><![CDATA[
			[npc.Name] places the seal onto your belly, and you marvel as it seems to sink into your skin. Your skin splits open painlessly the next second forming jagged teeth and a lolling tongue, however a testing reach for them has your hands waving through thin air, and brushing against your [pc.skinSkin+] half way into the illusionary maw.
		]]></NPCPlayer>
		<NPCPlayerRough><![CDATA[
			[npc.Name] presses the seal onto your belly, and holds it down until it seems to sink into your skin. Your skin splits open painlessly the next second forming jagged teeth and a lolling tongue, however a testing reach for them has your hands waving through thin air, and brushing against your [pc.skinSkin+] half way into the illusionary maw.
		]]></NPCPlayerRough>
		<NPCOtherNPC><![CDATA[
			[npc1.Name] places the seal onto [npc2.name]'s belly, and marvels as it seems to sink into [npc2.herHis] skin. [npc2.HerHis] skin splits open painlessly the next second forming jagged teeth and a lolling tongue.
		]]></NPCOtherNPC>
		<NPCOtherNPCRough><![CDATA[
			[npc1.Name] presses the seal onto [npc2.name]'s belly, and holds it down until it seems to sink into [npc2.herHis] skin. [npc2.HerHis] skin splits open painlessly the next second forming jagged teeth and a lolling tongue.
		]]></NPCOtherNPCRough>
	</replacementText>
	
</clothing>
