<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	<htmlContent tag="ZORU_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Trickster foxes from another world. Zoroark's true form bears black fur and an incredibly long mane of hair, but when disguised, very few can discern its true form.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="ZORU_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldDARKRED(Zoroark)]
	</p>
	<p>
		These fox-like beings are masters of illusion. Those that approach its home are left dangerously lost. It can convey its illusions to vast swaths of people at full power.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not to say this power is exclusively used for trickery, however, as Zoroark are known to be fiercely loyal. It oft uses its illusions to protect, or even to simply lift the spirits, of those it cares about. These are often other Zoroark, but can include interspecies partners as well.
	</p>
	<p>
		These vulpines can be found all across Dominion and especially Submission, their disguise magic being a highly sought feature, allowing them to take on the guise of whomever their partner decides they want to fuck. Some even desire the unique "thrill" of being dominated by "themselves".
	</p>
	<p>
		However, the arcane storms have recently put a hamper on the species' ability to transform, almost as if Lilith herself had placed a limitation to whatever "game" she's designed for her subjects
	</p>
	<p>
		Unlike normal foxes, or most other mammals for that matter, Zoroark deliver their offspring by laying eggs. Their Zorua form can briefly be seen before Lilith's magic forces them to grow.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using an Everstone on a Zoroark will cause them to regress into Zorua.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldDARKGREY(Zorua)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Less devious and more of a trickster than its more mature form. Zorua often use their illusions to trick and evade rather than dominate and shatter minds.
	</p>
	<p>
		Its more withdrawn nature often has it disguise itself as a child to blend into its surroundings. However, Zorua inexperienced in illusions often forget to hide their tails, exposing the ruse completely.
	</p>
	<p>
		Oddly, unlike Zoroark, feral Zorua are quadrupedal rather than bipedal, meaning Zoruataurs are theoretically possible.
	</p>
	<p>
		Like Zoroark, Zorua deliver their young with laid eggs. However, Lilith's magic doesn't appear to affect the newborns' growth, as they seem to hatch fully intelligent and capable of fighting and mating.
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeding a Rare Candy to a Zorua will cause them to evolve into Zoroark.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
</bookText>
