<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	<htmlContent tag="LUCARIO_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Jackal-like creatures from another world, attuned to people's life force. Lucario can be swiftly identified with their blue and black fur, sharp spikes, pointy ears, and long hair.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="LUCARIO_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldDARKBLUE(Lucario)]
	</p>
	<p>
		These jackal-like beings were already able to harness lifeforce in their world, capable of reading people's thoughts and emotions from over a kilometer away. Its power over "Aura" could pulverize even giant boulders into dust.
	</p>
	<p>
		The atmosphere of Lilith's Domain hasn't affected their ability to read said "Aura" in the slightest. If anything, it only made them even more attuned to this world's arcane essence.
	</p>
	<p>
		In turn, however, the standards of nobility Lucario tended to have in partners are both scarcely met, and greatly withered. The lustful nature of the arcane has affected their disposition greatly, making them more prone to lustful outbursts and ruts.
	</p>
	<p>
		Between those that attempt to hang onto some semblance of chivalry and those who embrace this world's debaucherous nature, these creatures can be found all over Dominion.
	</p>
	<p>
		Unlike normal jackals, or most other mammals for that matter, Lucario deliver their offspring by laying eggs. While their form at birth naturally shifts and evolves as a result of Lilith's arcane influence, their sexual disposition seems to be active even at a more supposedly juvenile age. (Though not quite as instantaneous as some other "monsters".)
	</p>
	<p>
		Their juvenile form, "Riolu" can briefly be seen when they hatch, but it's quickly passed over due to Lilith's growth magic, and Everstones don't seem capable of reverting them, likely due to their underdeveloped reproductive features.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldMAGENTA(Lilithian Lucario)]
	</p>
	<p>
		This unique breed of Lucario is one that came into being by the nature of this world. They have succumbed so deeply to Lilith's influence that their bodies have become more demonic in nature.
	</p>
	<p>
		The "pulse" that Lilithian Lucario seek is now that of pure ecstasy. They prey on virgins and passers-by, eager to engage in carnal breeding sessions. Their tails and their aphrodisiac venom enrapture their prey in a fit of lust.
	</p>
	<p>
		Their primary domain is Dominion, with many lurking in the bowels of Submission to find easier, and perhaps more willing prey, outside the Enforcers' watchful gaze.
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilithian Lucario, much like normal ones, deliver their offspring in a clutch of eggs.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
</bookText>
