<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PIXIE_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pixies are almost exclusively found in the western foloi forests and shinrin highlands, although the odd individual may sometimes be seen wandering the streets of Dominion. They are easily identifiable by their tiny frame and butterfly wings, those with arcane sensitivity may find them more easily as their body is incredibly dense with arcane.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="PIXIE_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pixies, like the folklore indicts, are very emotional, and can be generally seen as borderline bipolar individuals, they are easily affected by the surrounding emotions of people, displayed or not, the most popular explanation is that emotions have effects in the arcane. Despite their frail structure, making them easy targets to any household predators, they hang out in groups and their combined arcane proficiency along with their agility can prove to be a sigficant threat to any who choose to challenge their livelyhood, or accidentally stepped on their furniture.
	</p>
	<p>
		Pixies are, in the overwhelming majority, between 15 and 16 centimeters tall, but there has been a handful of cases in wich pixies measured over 2 feet tall: they are found to be extremely proficient with arcane alchemy, creating potent elixirs sold at a high price. They occupy an important role in large tribes as representatives of the group.
	</p>
	<p>
		Like most other races, pixies get affected by arcane storms. However, due to them being so attuned to the arcane, they may suffer manic events or be destabilized to the point of losing the capacity to fly.
	</p>
	<p>
		A pixie's offspring will always be a pixie unless their partner was demonic, leading to sprites; a more violent variant of pixies, found to have more arcane marks on their body.
	</p>
	<p>
		Indeed, one can easily gauge a pixie's arcane power based on their coverings, the more markings are present on one's body the higher their affinity with the arcane is, if one's skin shimmers it increases it further and if one sparkles their affinity is even higher. it is unknown wether or not if pixies with a freckled face are subjected to increased affinity.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</bookText>
