<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	<htmlContent tag="RALTS_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ivory creatures from another world that resonate with the emotions of the people around them. These beautiful beings, especially Gardevoir, are exceptionally popular among slave traders.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="RALTS_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldGREEN(Gardevoir)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Known as "The Embrace". Its dress resembles a guardian angel, and the horns protruding from its chest and back are rumored to be a single horn attached to its heart.
	</p>
	<p>
		These beings are fiercely loyal to those they bond with, easily willing to give up their lives if need be. As a result, many knights and Enforcers come seeking their aid. As a last ditch effort, a Gardevoir may expend all of its arcane, psychokinetic energy at once, often creating a singularity in space.
	</p>
	<p>
		On the other hand, their delicate, voloptuous features make them an easy target for slave traders and those who aim to take advantage of their bodies. Truly no one can escape their allure. As a result, wild Gardevoir outside the gates of Dominion are very rarely seen.
	</p>
	<p>
		Gardevoir conceive their offspring as eggs. Once they hatch, Lilith's magics quickly hasten their growth into Gardevoir themselves.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using an Everstone on a Gardevoir will cause them to regress into Kirlia.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldDARKGREEN(Gallade)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Known as "The Blade" after the long sword-like features protruding from its elbows. Its head, crest, and body resembles a noble knight.
	</p>
	<p>
		These warriors are masters of swordsmanship and chivalry, and are just as loyal as Gardevoir. It only lets out its savage side protecting those it cares about, again, making it heavily sought after as the ideal Enforcer.
	</p>
	<p>
		It also possesses incredible foresight that not only allows it to read its opponents moves in battle, but also lets it sense the emotions of those in need.
	</p>
	<p>
		Gallade are typically an exclusively male branch of the Ralts family, but the offspring they father often grow into Gallade, despite usually requiring the power of a certain stone. The magic of Lilith's Realm never ceases to bring new mysteries.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using an Everstone on a Gallade will cause them to regress into Kirlia.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldLIGHTGREEN(Kirlia)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Known as "The Emotion" due to its connection to the people around it. In the presence of positive emotions, it becomes more beautiful and joyously dances.
	</p>
	<p>
		The horns on its head are said to amplify its psychic power. While not as potent of an arcane fighter as Gardevoir or Gallade, its brain is still advanced enough to see into the future, altering the scenery around itself with spacial distortions and mirages.
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite its highly effeminate looks, Kirlia and Gardevoir are just as likely to be male as they are female, though many in Lilith's Realm don't seem to care.
	</p>
	<p>
		Kirlia also lay eggs to rear their young. Once they hatch, they evolve immediately to this pivotal point of their growth.
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeding a Rare Candy to a Kirlia will cause them to evolve into Gardevoir.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using a Dawn Stone on a male Kirlia will cause them to evolve into Gallade.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using an Everstone on a Kirlia will cause them to regress into Ralts.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldLIGHTGREEN(Ralts)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Known as "The Feeling", via the horns upon its head that can capture the warm feelings of the people around it.
	</p>
	<p>
		The emotions of its surroundings drive most of its actions. When people are joyous, it's joyous in turn. If people are hostile, it hides away from the conflict.
	</p>
	<p>
		Ralts are rather reclusive by nature, but encountering someone with a welcoming heart can draw it closer. The corrupt nature of Lilith's Realm, however, means that these types of people are quickly becoming harder to come by.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although Ralts may appear childlike at a glance, they are perfectly intelligent, cognizant, and sexually able from the moment they hatch. Thusly, a Ralts's offspring doesn't seem affected by Lilith's growth magic whatsoever.
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeding a Rare Candy to a Ralts will cause them to evolve into Kirlia.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
</bookText>
