<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	<htmlContent tag="FOCCO_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Mysterious fox-like creatures from another world. Members of this race have large tufts of fur near their ears distinct from regular fennecs.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="FOCCO_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldRED(Delphox)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Fox mages with power over fire and the mind. By focusing on the flame of a lit branch, it can see into the future. Like most creatures with power over the arcane, it frequently combats visions of lust due to Lilith's influence.
	</p>
	<p>
		Its dominion over fire is incredibly potent. It can enrapture its foes in a vortex of flame hot enough to boil iron.
	</p>
	<p>
		Delphox can be found in the same places as most foxes and youkos. They seem to have enough self-control to not stray into seedier places as the likes of Submission.
	</p>
	<p>
		Unlike normal foxes, or most other mammals for that matter, Delphox deliver their offspring by laying eggs. Once they hatch, Lilith's magics quickly hasten their growth into Delphox themselves.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using an Everstone on a Delphox will cause them to regress into Braixen.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldORANGE(Braixen)]
	</p>
	<p>
		A scorching hot fox with a branch in its tail. The friction from removing it sets it alight, allowing it to be used as a signal for allies and a conduit for its fire spells.
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite its effeminate, witch-like appearance, only about 1 in 8 Braixen are actually female, though many in Lilith's Realm don't seem to care.
	</p>
	<p>
		Braixen also lay eggs to rear their young.  Their Fennekin form can briefly be seen before Lilith's magic forces them to grow.
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeding a Rare Candy to a Braixen will cause them to evolve into Delphox.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using an Everstone on a Braixen will cause them to regress into Fennekin.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldGINGER(Fennekin)]
	</p>
	<p>
		These small foxes can often be seen chewing on twigs. They're not just full of hot air, one could literally fry an egg on the air their ears give off.
	</p>
	<p>
		Oddly enough, the feral form of these creatures are quadrupedal, like most foxes, instead of upright like its two evolved forms. As a result, it's the only species of which true "taurs" are possible.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not much else is known about this species or its line as a whole, almost as if the documents describing these creatures should have written entries in more than one pair of games.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although Fennekin may appear young at a glance, they are perfectly intelligent, cognizant, and sexually able from the moment they hatch. Thusly, a Fennekin's offspring doesn't seem affected by Lilith's growth magic whatsoever.
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeding a Rare Candy to a Fennekin will cause them to evolve into Braixen.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
</bookText>
